owsfinance.com 2016-11-21

# Legal Disclaimers and Privacy Policy

## Disclosure

I maintain affiliate relationships with several companies. Most of these are programs that I have used and love. When I do not love the program, I say so. What this means is that when I write about a program or product I love and include a link, I get a commission, which helps support this site.

Sometimes a company compensates me (usually in the form of a gift card) to write a post about something I find interesting or useful. When that happens, I mention that I have been compensated at the end of the post. I do write about companies I am affiliated with, but my opinions are always truthful. I try to include the positives and negatives of any products I write about. If you have any questions about the above companies, feel free to contact me with any questions. I’d be glad to discuss them with you.

I also run paid ads in my sidebar. Some ads are affiliate ads for companies I love. I hand pick these ads, because they’re companies and products I personally use. All other ads like Google Adsense are random, and I do not endorse them.

## Policies

### Comment Policy

I enjoy comments, good discussion, and alternative viewpoints. You are always welcome to leave a comment if you have something to add to the conversation, a question to ask, or even a viewpoint different than my own. However, I do ask that you be respectful in voicing your opinions, both to me and to other commentators. I reserve the right to remove any comments that are obviously meant to be inflammatory or comments that are spam.

### Link Exchange Policy

I do not participate in link exchanges. I do not have time to respond to emails requesting link exchanges. I’m sorry.

## Privacy

The privacy of our visitors to OwsFinance.com is important to us. At OwsFinance.com, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit OwsFinance.com, and how we safeguard your information. We never sell your personal information to third parties.

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocal) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This could include only showing you a popup once in your visit, or the ability to login to some of our features, such as forums.

We also use third party advertisements on OwsFinance.com to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

## Contact Info

You can reach me at **worksavelive@gmail.com**.

### Disclaimer and Stuff

The articles are written by personal finance enthusiasts (not certified professionals) based on their personal experience. What works for them may or may not work for you, and you should always consult a financial advisor before making important financial decisions.

In accordance with FTC guidelines, we disclose that we have a financial relationship with companies mentioned in this website. This may include receiving access to free products and services for product and service reviews and giveaways.

Any references to third party products, rates, or websites are subject to change without notice. We do our best to maintain current information, but due to the rapidly changing environment, some information may have changed since it was published. Please do the appropriate research before participating in any third party offers.

For additional information, please review our legal disclaimers and privacy policy.
